

Enrico Colautti

Warszawa, Poland

phone: +48 604 886 466 email: doctorc@o2.pl

LinkedIn: goo.gl/VNN6vv

Github: goo.gl/ITR5Z9

LAST Projects

2022-Current – **Netigate.** Survey app. Responsible for frontend refactoring and debugging of legacy code and developing new apps including AI LLM for feedback generation. React, Typescript, REST, Websocket, LLM, OpenAI, accessibility.

2021 – Imperative. Peer coaching app. Responsible for frontend refactoring and debugging. React, Coffescript, Javascript, REST, audio, video, responsiveness, accessibility.

2021 – Myopolis. Customer service online app. Responsible for frontend debugging, refactoring and development of new features. React, Typescript, REST, Websockets, audio, responsiveness.

2020-2021 – **Virbe.AI**. Animated chatbot with AI. Responsible for frontend development from scratch. React, Web Component, Typescript, audio, REST, Websocket, Graphics, Babylon.js, Animation.

2018-2020 – Veewme. Real estate services app. Frontend Lead for the second version of the app. React, Typescript, GraphQL, Responsiveness

WORK Experience

2004 - Current Positive Software Enrico Colautti.

Own company. Software development, freelance programmer, web development, working on B2B basis.

2008 eZee Software, Ireland.

Software debugging and customization for the Polish market. Delphi

1997 - 2004 HF Lingua sp. z o. o.

Language school, co-owner and administrator, developer of internal use software.

1997 - 2001 Telesoft Communication sp. z o. o.

Software house, co-owner and CTO, author of the first program in Poland for the preparation of public tenders.

1995 - 1997 Softlab sp. z o. o.

Data transmission software development.

EDUCATION

2018 Udacity. Mobile Web Specialist. Google Developer Nano-degree Scholarship.

2009 Akademia Leona Kozmińskiego, Warszawa. Business Management.

2007 Wyższa Szkoła Administracji i Biznesu im. E. Kwiatkowskiego, Gdynia. Public tenders in Poland and EU. Post-graduate specialization.

1993-1995 Uniwersytet Warszawski. Polish language.

1985 - 1991 Universita` degli studi di Udine, Italy. Computer Science MSc, with database design specialization.

SUMMARY

I have been around long enough to remember Commodore 64, black and white TV and dot-matrix printers. With over 30 years of programming experience from Assembler, through SQL, C, Pascal, Delphi and Python, I now specialize in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Typescript and React.

SKILLS

Javascript, Typescript, React, RTK, HTML5, CSS3, Git, Vite, Webpack, Chart.js, a11y, Babylon.js, Websocket, REST, LLM, responsiveness and accessibility for web pages, junior developers mentoring, frontend architecture

LANGUAGES

Italian: native English: fluent Polish: fluent

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997r o Ochronie Danych Osobowych; tekst jednolity: Dz. U. 2016 r. poz. 922).